Jhal
Hua Hai
Shri Krishna Everyone 100 Witness Bana Kasana and
Lizer Khushboo Fried Rice Flour Mission
Possible To Withdraw Death Awareness Staff
Question for Us Of Not Active Yes So
Excited to Medium to Share Mix
Question with You All Self Question with You Thought Question
in our screens and you can see me
for you as a
responsible citizen how you will help to
reduce pollution is responsible citizen
how you can help to reduce
pollution so your answers are on your screen
by electric that ek pal greater
PUCCA idiot Michael Service tab
about so you can choose any one of these answers
you can join us
according to you you can be a part of fish so by
participating in the square miles and
you can also you can fans mini
starting price writing to you you
can see this online contest and you can
win prizes everyday definitely like this is
for  Your family to you can now you can win
prizes for your family like for kids
helmet and rollick umm a darkar se fix
for your family with you for you and it's amazing
to be a part of the question a
gyan surya question I repeat it again for you
today responsible citizen
of
surya helps to reduce pollution in the
electric bike or electric vehicle1
set up to see the song of the answer juice
here on our
youtube channel which is our page you
can go and give your answer here you will start here
you can go down and share your answer with us
and you can win very
exciting prizes as I
told you and this is ours this is on daily basis
this is on daily basis you people can come
we can join and you
can win share exciting prizes we will
come with you every 2 hours we will share
a new question with you every time
you can answer it  You can answer and the
most interesting thing is that
it is not limited like you can come the whole day and
you can participate in all 5 of our questions
and can give multiple give
speeches, this is mostly happening,
you can participate in one question only once, it will
not consider you again,
but in the second question, if you are ignorant, you can
message come and join and share your answers with us,
you can also connect your family, friends and those people with it,
they also have the opportunity to
come and join this campaign and get many
gift seats, you now cross only with Team A,
as I told you that Firoz
Saifi is another topic today, we will talk about road
safety and our
topic means our questions will
also be strongly related to it,
basically Steve Waugh is related to road safety,
so that
if all the people get to know about it through this,
through our campaign, that you and by
joining us and one  We can bring new changes to our
Indian Rupee. Let me show you the question this time.
Okay, it is Bhindi on my screen. Know, it is very important
to the road.
Haridwar road traffic, which engineers have
drowned. This is road traffic entries, this is a
very important issue
in our day-to-day life. Everyday
we live, that is, we go out on the road
and every day because we have to go to
office, some have to go to their
relatives somewhere or have to
go in someone else's name, so we have to use these attacks every day,
whether we
use a pedestrian or we start by car
or if we just click on a two-wheeler,
somewhere or the other we are
connected to the road, so
making our daily process our responsibility is very important
to make car rolls
only for everyone. It is a
not-for-profit, but if you
subscribe for that, or we have to
make our daily process very important for every subject.  It's important, but
keep all those things in mind. If we
can bring small changes into our lives, then perhaps
we can make our daily lives better. For example, the
small rules
that relate to our lives,
meaning those related to Barot City, we
all know
what rules we should follow in the delivery area, what we should
not do, and
what things can get us fined. So,
we
all know what we should do, what we should
not do, and which districts we
can drive in. We don't have to get fined because there's a
traffic police here, so
we have to do those things that we might get fined.
But if
we think about it for our
safety, for the safety of our loved ones, then
we can bring about changes. If we
all know that never drink and drive word,
we go to parties,
we check it, and then
drive back.  Which is very risky,
you don't just put your life, maybe someone else is
going through that, you also put his life
in relationships, because of a small
mistake, instead of driving you
can take a license or you can take some other license
or you can stop at your friend's place,
so we can avoid
that thing that we should not drink and drive, drink
and drive, we should tell everyone, just
follow that thing, this
11.2 Create Road Awareness Rohit Shetty and
every day on the 52nd seat belt office told you,
why is change important only
because if we do not wear a seat belt, it
can put our life in danger
because the car is in this weather
and if there is a crush, then there can be a
lot of damage to your body,
then if you do not wear a seat belt, then
now you cannot even save yourself from gas,
it becomes very risky, if there is a very
good, big crush, then we
all know that the first thing is important,
but if we  Rishi, if you want to go nearby or
go a little far, then we will
appoint you.
If you send us for a short distance, then
you have to wear a seat belt. It is very important
because if we
can pick up the changes one by one only. If you wear a seat belt, then
you can say to someone else that
please see, you are chief butter paper. This is very important. There are many
wells and this is a
safe distance between you. You must have seen the name of this
on Indian roads. It is very difficult
because when we are coming from office,
going to office, business and
measured cars, at that time there is a lot of video traffic, it is
bumper-to-bumper driving,
there is no space and if you give a little space by mistake, then
two flower sellers enter in it, which is very very
risky. We
need to maintain a little distance and then bring our changes, that and religious which puts  To
avoid this, one thing we
should maintain this much distance is 216, you must have heard
about China in the 216 rule and it is
necessary for us to maintain a distance between ourselves
and Ram, so much distance should be maintained between us that the
back tyre of the tyre in front of us is visible to us,
so we will maintain that distance between us, so
if we face any option risk somewhere, then by
maintaining that thing
we can save ourselves from having a high amount, Vijay
Rally is a small important thing that we should
always stop our vehicle
before the crossing, we will
leave space for distance on it
because it is not to be used only by the attackers,
it has to be used by everyone every day
and we have to
make that route suitable for this, so by taking care of such small
things we
can make our Bluetooth suitable and at this time
we can join this camp and this campaign,
now you should not use it, this is our right,
which we  People, please dive into
our question now.
You can participate in the next one and
be a part of this entire campaign and
win exciting prizes. So, you
can see what is visible on my screen, our
third question today,
I am giving you, A Responsible
Citizen, How will you help reduce
pollution by little boy, girl, get up to
cigarettes, right there under the best. So, you saw
that it is such a simple question, we all know this. So,
mothers, you should join as much as possible, bring
your family members and your friends to
this,
you have a chance to win an exciting gift
and not only this, you can ask just one,
you have a chance to
win multiple gifts as well. So, participate
and this, we will
display 5 questions to you throughout the day,
our answers will be shared with you and
every time, we will display one question to you every 2 hours,
which will last for 2 hours.
In 2 hours, you can answer this cream of ours by
going down and
clicking on the link in the description. Now you
can go to our YouTube page and answer there.
You
can also go to our Facebook page and answer your answers. Our
results will be announced to you in the evening.
Our issue comes very speaking at a
no clothes pimples. That Tinku clock will be
announced to you
and you can always join.
You will also have research on our webpage. The ability of this is that a
lot of entries come for one question.
Fund case will be to stay
believe and we will take out the rebels and then
Appu will share the belief also. You can join part of
the and from daily basis. If
you want, you can join our show at 10:00 pm.
You will get the answers
which will be there. We will announce our
delivery speed answers there, that is, the
names of our viewers, so
everyone is blown away, one more chance  Through this
route, the message from Africa which we
want to give, whatever was there or not, whatever is
connected to it,
we want to reach you somewhere today, we want
you to join us,
become a part of our campaign, help us in completing the Drive Safe Doo DCO mission,
please brother, part of the A, I will
tell you the question again in the question space,
you must go to our website and
register your answer, so the question is today,
responsible citizen, you will help to
reduce pollution in electrical being A
B C D E F pressure and thank you for the beach,
after to and will subscribe, after to all
my friends, on
my record, Shrikant, to you, she will give the
name of the state of question and
youth India part of the best all Shoaib
School, thank you so much, u jhal jhal jhal jhal jhal